Guide to the Lewis Lloyd Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Lewis Lloyd papers
1880-1994
1961-1994
YCAL MSS 752
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
49.88
(59 boxes) + 33 broadsides, 11 art
Lloyd, Lewis L.
Arrangement
Organized into three groupings: I. May 1995 Acquisition, II. October 1995 Acquisition, III. February 1996 Acquisition.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 97 and 103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 96 (reel-to-reel tape and 8mm film): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Lewis Lloyd, 1995-1996.
Scope and Contents
The papers of Lewis Lloyd include correspondence, writings, business records, photographs, artwork, audio tapes, video tapes, printed material, production programs, posters, books and ephemera. The papers document his work between 1962 and 1989 in a number of professional positions: as owner of the off-Broadway Pocket Theater; manager of the Merce Cunningham Dance Company; general manager for the Brooklyn Academy of Music; program director for the New York State Council for the Arts; and as a consultant to television and radio stations, dance companies and art museums in the Northeast. Lloyd also was an avid collector of theatre and dance memorabilia. Along with his personal papers are books, production programs, posters, photographs and other materials documenting the history and productions of Alvin Ailey, Ballets Russes, the American Ballet Company, New York City Ballet, Twyla Tharp, as well as dancers and choreographers.
Biographical / Historical
Lewis Lloyd was born in 1938, graduated with a B.A. from Yale University in 1960, and received a Master's degree in public administration from The John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University in 1974. In addition to owning and directing the Pocket Theater in New York from 1962 to 1974, he was a manager for the Merce Cunningham Dance Company, general manager for the Brooklyn Academy of Music from 1968 to 1972, and was the program director for the Performing Arts, New York State Council for the Arts from 1972 to 1974. He also was manager of finance and administration for WGBH from 1975 to 1980, and was an independent consultant from 1980 to 1985, working with The Entertainment Channel in New York; BBI Productions, Channel 5 in Boston; the architectural firm of Skidmore Owings & Merrill; and the Boston Redevelopment Authority. From 1989 to 1992 he was vice president of finance and administration at New England Conservatory in Boston. Lloyd also served on the boards of the Boston Ballet, the Twyla Tharp Dance Company, and Boston's Institute for Contemporary Art.
Arts administrators -- United States; Dance -- Russia; Dance -- United States; Theater -- United States; Theatrical producers and directors -- United States; Audiovisual materials; Photographs; Posters; Arts administrators -- United States -- 20th Century; Theatrical producers and directors -- United States -- 20th Century; Lloyd, Lewis L.; Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater; Ballets russes; Brooklyn Academy of Music; Merce Cunningham Dance Company; New York City Ballet; New York State Council on the Arts; Pocket Theater (Organization: New York, N.Y.); Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation
- May 1995 Acquisition, 1880-1984; Series I; 45.46; (53 boxes) + 33 broadsides, 11 art
  Scope and Contents
  This acquisition contains correspondence, writings, reports, notes, printed material, photographs, art work, posters, and audiovisual materials, including records of The Pocket Theater; the Brooklyn Academy of Music; the New York State Council for the Arts and other companies for whom Lloyd served as administrator or consultant. Also included are materials relating to dance and theater companies including the Ballets Russes; the Merce Cunningham Dance Company,Twyla Tharp Dance, the Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater.
  Arrangement
  Arranged in order received.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 103 contains audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence related to Quartet Productions, Sap of Life (including invoices, investor files, actors contracts, and advertising), 1961; 50 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence related to Quartet Productions, Sap of Life (including invoices, investor files, actors contracts, and advertising), 1961; 64 (Box 2)
  - Sap of Life, Vexations programs, clippings, correspondence; script for Sap of Life, by Rick Matlay, Jr.; script for The Color of Darkness, by Ellen M. Violett, 1961-1963; 17 (Box 3)
  - Sap of Life, Vexations programs, clippings, correspondence; script for The Color of Darkness, by Ellen M. Violett, 1961-1963; 9 (Box 4)
  - Scripts (19 in total), 1961-1963; 14 (Box 4)
  - Scripts (19 in total), 1961-1963; 7 (Box 5)
  - Pocket Theatre correspondence related to construction and various productions, 1962-1968; 30 (Box 5)
  - Pocket Theatre correspondence related to construction and various productions, 1962-1968; 35 (Box 6)
  - Pocket Theatre business papers, business correspondence, performance receipts, ticket stubs, unused tickets, miscellaneous bills and receipts, 1962-1974; 33 (Box 6)
  - Pocket Theatre business papers, business correspondence, performance receipts, ticket stubs, unused tickets, miscellaneous bills and receipts, 1962-1974; 13 (Box 7)
  - Business papers, cancelled checks from Sans Souci Theatre Corporation; Intervale Theatre Corporation business correspondence; Twin Theater Inc. correspondence; Pocket Theatre correspondence, 1962-1974; 28 (Box 8)
  - Files related to the Pocket Theatre and Comet Theatre including lobby card, photographs, and correspondence, undated; 67 (Box 9)
  - Files related to the Pocket Theatre and Comet Theatre including lobby card, photographs, and correspondence, undated; 22 (Box 10)
  - Photographs, programs, clippings, correspondence, business papers relating to Merce Cunningham and Robert Joffrey Ballet, and other papers, 1963-1964; 13 (Box 10)
  - Photographs, programs, clippings, correspondence, business papers relating to Merce Cunningham and Robert Joffrey Ballet, and other papers, 1963-1964; 10 (Box 11)
  - MANA Productions cash book, correspondence; files on U.S. colleges, 1966; 27 (Box 11)
  - MANA Productions cash book, correspondence; files on U.S. colleges, 1966; 83 (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, clippings, and programs relating to various dance groups in New York, 1965; 49 (Box 13)
  - Correspondence, clippings, and programs relating to various dance groups in New York, 1965; 5 (Box 14)
  - BAM management and publicity notebooks; National Dance Foundation notebook; programs and clippings; file relating to management of Festival Orchestra; miscellaneous periodicals, 1965-1966; 12 (Box 14)
  - Programs and clippings; file relating to management of Festival Orchestra; miscellaneous periodicals, 1965-1966; 10 (Box 15)
  - Programs and clippings; letters, programs and clippings on MANA productions; Festival Orchestra Society New York notebook; Association of American Dance Companies; Labor Relations in the Performing Arts, 1966-1967; 5 (Box 15)
  - Programs and clippings; letters, programs and clippings on MANA productions; Association of American Dance Companies; Labor Relations in the Performing Arts, 1966-1967; 12 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and programs relating to Merce Cunningham, including programs from the Latin American tour, 1968; 13 (Box 16)
  - Correspondence and programs relating to Merce Cunningham, including programs from the Latin American tour, 1968; 9 (Box 17)
  - Clipping file on Lenny Bruce; miscellaneous periodicals; correspondence relating to Niels Kehlet, ABC European tour, and the American Ballet Theater, 1969; 16 (Box 17)
  - Association of American Dance Companies notebook; clipping file on Lenny Bruce; miscellaneous periodicals; correspondence relating to Niels Kehlet, ABC European tour, and American Ballet Theater, 1969; 9 (Box 18)
  - Files relating to management of art groups, including Bejart, Kingsborough Community College and others; programs of various groups, 1970; 13 (Box 18)
  - Files relating to management of art groups, including Bejart, Kingsborough Community College and others; programs of various groups, 1970; 14 (Box 19)
  - BAM clippings and programs; blank stock certificate for BAM, 1908; file on Bejart company; file on 1972 subsidy for BAM; file on New York State Council on the Arts, 1908, 1971-1972; 29 (Box 20)
  - First American Theatre Conference, BAM programs, City Center programs, correspondence relating to performing arts program, New York State Council on the Arts, 1973-1974; 26 (Box 21)
  - AFTRA and other union agreements with WGBH-TV; contract forms, WGBH-TV; miscellaneous reports and publications; file of correspondence and business papers relating to New Music in New Hampshire, 1973-1979; 11 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous reports and studies; notebook on Opera New England; miscellaneous programs; NYSCA correspondence, 1974; 12 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous reports and studies; miscellaneous programs; NYSCA correspondence, 1974; 8 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence relating to various activities, including NYSCA, Massachusetts Council on the Arts, Citizens Committee for the Arts, and WGBH-TV; miscellaneous reports, 1975; 14 (Box 24)
  - WGBH in-house correspondence notebook; correspondence relating to various activities, including NYSCA, Massachusetts Council on the Arts, Citizens Committee for the Arts, and WGBH-TV; miscellaneous reports, 1975; 10 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence including clippings and programs; Dance World; miscellaneous dance periodicals; articles by Richard Nielson; 14 proposals for WGBH programming, 1976-1980; 10 (Box 25)
  - WGBH in-house correspondence notebook; miscellaneous correspondence including clippings and programs; Dance World; miscellaneous dance periodicals; articles by Richard Nielson; 14 proposals for WGBH programming, 1976-1980; 8 (Box 26)
  - WGBH union agreements and fax rates notebook; WGBH correspondence; miscellaneous programs, including Upstairs, Downstairs souvenir program for the last episode; 2 notebooks, Dance Advisory Panel Book, 1977 December and October, 1977-1978; 10 (Box 27)
  - Boston Theatre district notebook; miscellaneous reports; miscellaneous correspondence, press releases and clippings, 1979; 8 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous reports; miscellaneous correspondence, press release, and clippings, 1979; 13 (Box 29)
  - Programs, 1930-1960; 4 (Box 29)
  - Programs, 1930-1960; 11 (Box 30)
  - Books, undated; 7 (Box 31)
  - Dance Magazine and other periodicals, 1966-1973; 5 (Box 31)
  - Dance Magazine and other periodicals, 1966-1973; 14 (Box 32)
  - Framed photograph of George M. Cohen, autographed; photograph of Otis Skinner, autographed 1932; Dance Panel Advisory Book 1978; 8 still photographs of Sap of Life, 1961, 1932,1961,1978; 10 (Box 33)
  - Periodicals, 1963-1971; 7 (Box 33)
  - Periodicals, 1963-1971; 6 (Box 34)
  - Programs, 1921-1969; 7 (Box 34)
  - Programs, 1921-1969; 9 (Box 35)
  - Books and periodicals, including Dance Magazine (incomplete), 1951-1964; 4 (Box 35)
  - Books and periodicals, including Dance Magazine (incomplete), 1951-1964; 9 (Box 36)
  - WGBH in-house correspondence, notebook; notebooks and file relating to National Endowment for the Arts; dance panel advisory books #1 and #2, 1978; 17 (Box 37)
  - Periodicals and miscellaneous papers, 1964-1970; 10 (Box 38)
  - Periodicals, 1951-1970; 13 (Box 39)
  - Periodicals, 1951-1970; 4 (Box 40)
  - Playbills, programs, and miscellaneous papers, 1968-1981; 13 (Box 40)
  - Playbills, programs, and miscellaneous papers; collage (framed) by James Waring, 1965?, 1961-1985; 5 (Box 41)
  - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation brochure, 1987 (multiple copies); NY State Council on the Arts Annual Report, 1972-73., 1987, 1972-1973; 5 (Box 41)
  - 6 photographs, 1971; 6 (Box 41)
  - Phil Glass, Merce, Twyla, Theater district, NYCB. #103, 1984; 11 (Box 41)
  - Phil Glass, Merce, Twyla, Theater district, NYCB. #103, 1984; 6 (Box 42)
  - George's House, Dan Wagoner, undated; YCALMSS752_0003; 1; 00:26:18 (Box 103, Item barcode 39002102339463)
  - TV and file materials; RCTV from start to finish; scripts of Virginia Woolf's To the Lighthouse, etc. #102, 1976-1982; 18 (Box 42)
  - TV and file materials; RCTV from start to finish; scripts of Virginia Woolf's To the Lighthouse, etc. #102, 1976-1982; 6 (Box 43)
  - Lewis L. Lloyd bookplates, undated (Box 43)
  - #2 "Balieff's "Chauve-Souris" program, 1924-1925 (Box 43)
  - #4 BAM stock certificate, [1900?] (Box 43)
  - #7 Les Ballets 1933, exhibition catalogue (Box 43)
  - #14 Anton Dolin, photograph, 1977 (Box 43)
  - #18 Anna Pavlova The Incomparable, program book, undated (Box 43)
  - #19 Anna Pavlova, souvenir book, 1924-1925 (Box 43)
  - #20 Anna Pavlova and her Ballet Russe, program, undated (Box 43)
  - #21 Anna Pavlova, souvenir program, 1924 (Box 43)
  - #22 Mlle. Anna Pavlova, Prima Ballerina, program, [1910?] (Box 43)
  - #25 Dance International, program, 1937 (Box 43)
  - #26 Letters from Irina Baronova, with photos, 1940-1980 (Box 43)
  - #28 Mumaw, program book, 1930's (Box 43)
  - #31 Impressions of the Russian Ballet 1919: Petrouchka, written by C.W. Beaumont (Box 43)
  - #37 American Ballet Theater, 1969 (Box 43)
  - #42 Grand Ballet de Monte Carlo, program, 1949 (Box 43)
  - #53 Blast at Ballet, book, 1938 (Box 43)
  - #70 Merce Cunningham & Dance Co., booklet, 1964 (Box 43)
  - #82 Merce Cunningham & Dance Co., handbill, Joyce Theater, 1984 (Box 43)
  - #84 Merce Cunningham, Roeder Gallery, invitations, 1984 (Box 43)
  - #88 Mikail Mordkin and his Russian Ballet, program, [1926?] (Box 43)
  - #89 The Mordkin Ballet, souvenir book, 1937-1938 (Box 43)
  - #90 International Ballet, program, 1948 (Box 43)
  - #101 Ruth St. Denis, Ted Shawn, program, 1924 (Box 43)
  - #102 Ruth St. Denis, Temple Studio, program, undated (Box 43)
  - #103 Ruth St. Denis, American tour, program, 1923-1924 (Box 43)
  - #104 Ballets Russes, booklet, 1916-1917 (Box 43)
  - #105 Ballets Russes, prospectus, 1915 (Box 43)
  - #107 Serge Diaghilev's Ballets Russes, booklet, 1916-1917 (Box 43)
  - #108 Les Ballets Russes de Serge Diaghilev, booklet, 1930 (Box 43)
  - #109 Catalogue de L'Exposition Retrospective De, booklet, 1930 (Box 43)
  - #110 Diaghilev's card, framed, 1922-1924 (Box 43)
  - #111 Letter from Princess Wolkonsky, 1954 June 15 (Box 44)
  - #112 Conductor's contract, Ballets Russes, 1917 June 30 (Box 44)
  - #113 Conductor's contract, Ballets Russes, 1920-1921 (Box 44)
  - #114 Photo of Tamara Karsavina, 1928 April 4 (Box 44)
  - #115 Letters from Tamara Karsavina, with photographs, 1955, 1959 (Box 44)
  - #116 Program of service, Tamara Karsavina, 1978 September 27 (Box 44)
  - #117 Photograph of Olga Spessivtzeva and card, 1924 (Box 44)
  - #118 Photograph of Olga Spessivtzeva and card, undated (Box 44)
  - #119 Photograph of Spessivtzeva, Dolin, and Gilpin, 1979 (Box 44)
  - #120 Photograph of Bronislava Nijinska, with letter, 1937 (Box 44)
  - #121 Letter from Bronislava Nijinska, 1938 June 3 (Box 44)
  - #122 Photograph of Olga Spessivtzeva, with cards, [1969?] (Box 102 (Oversize))
  - #127 How Beautiful Upon the Mountain, promotional book, 1943 (Box 44)
  - #128 Ted Shawn and His Men Dancers, souvenir book, 1938 (Box 44)
  - #129 Letter from Lincoln Kirstein, 1983 February 7 (Box 44)
  - #130 All-Man Performance, reprint, 1936 (Box 44)
  - #131 Ted Shawn and his Men Dancers, souvenir book, 1936-1937 (Box 44)
  - #143 Ballet Society, booklet, 1946-1947 (Box 44)
  - Posters and photographs
    - Alan Stone Gallery. Exhibition and Sale of Works by Artists to the Foundation for the Contemporary Performance Arts, poster., 1962 February 25-March 2 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Chelsea Theater Center of Brooklyn. Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster., undated (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Six Lectures at the Poetry Center. N.O. Brown, Peter Yates, Buckminster Fuller, Merce Cunningham, Harold Rosenberg, and Marshall McLuhan, poster., [1966?] March 31-May 7 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Feldman/Brown. The Foundation for the Contemporary Performance Arts presents Music for Orchestra & Chorus by Morton Feldman and Earle Brown, poster., 1963, October 11 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - The Festival Orchestra of New York. Messiah. Carnegie Hall, poster., 1966, December 21 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - The Paper Bag Players. Hunter College Playhouse, poster (2 copies), 1973 January-April (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - J. S. Bach. The St. Matthew Passion. The Festival Orchestra of New York, Lincoln Center, poster., 1967 January 20-March 24 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - American Ballet Company. Eliot Feld, director. Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster., 1969 October 21-November 1 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - The Merce Cunningham Dance Company. Sadlers Wells Theater, poster. (#74), (no year) July 27 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Decor by William Roberts for Group 20 Players, Wellesley, watercolor and ink sketch., 1957 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Paradise Now. The Living Theater at Brooklyn Academy of Music, photo by Max Waldmen, Judith Molina in foreground, photograph. (#60), 1968 (Box 45 (Oversize))
    - Aileen Passloff and Dance Company. Four Works. Music by Richard Maxfield, designs by Claes Oldenburg, James Waring. Fashion Institute of Technology. (#16), 1962 January 20 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Vexations. Score xeroxed by John Cage, poster., 1963 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Eight Choreographers: Merce Cunningham, Martha Graham, and othes in photograph by Jack Mitchell taken at Martha Graham's New York Studio (#83), 1968 September 12 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Merce Cunningham & Dance Company, Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster. (#76), 1967 May 15-26 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Photograph of Richard Cyzlakin, The Constant Prince, by Max Waldman, 1969. (#61) (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Cambodian dancer at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, photograph by Max Waldeman. (#59), 1969 (Box 46 (Oversize))
    - Claes Oldenburg. Green Gallery, poster. (#33), 1962 September 24-October 20 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Twyla Tharp Dance on Broadway at the Winter Garden, poster. (#135), 1981 September 22-October 18 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Twyla Tharp Dance on Broadway, The Catherine Wheel, flyer for the 1981 September production, designed by Santo Loquasto, poster. (#134) (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Rosalind Newman and Dancers, The Joyce Theater, 1984 March 28-April 1, poster. (#99/100?) (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Wolf Moon Waltz for Six Dancers, by Meg Harper, The Cunningham Studio, poster. (#62), 1964 November 15-17 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Promotional photograph for The Sap of Life, photograph. (#56), 1961 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - James Waring & Dance Company. Fred Herko, Yvonne Rainer, Arlene Rothelein, Lucinda Childs, Gary Gross, and Deborah Hay in Phrases music by Erik Satie....Judson Memorial Church, poster. (#45), 1963 August 25-26 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, Saville Theatre, lecture and concert by John Cage, 1966 November 26, poster. (#75), 1966 November 23-December 3 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - New Music at the Pocket Theater Benefit, the Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, Vexations, first complete performance of Erik Satie's 14 hour piece, by the Pocket Theater Relay Team, players include John Cage, David Tudor, Viola Farber, others TBA, [no year] September 9, poster. (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - New Music at the Pocket Theater Benefit, the Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, music of Edward Boagni, George Brecht, John Cage, Al Hansen, John Herbert McDowell, La Monte Young; music of Joseph Bryd, Philip Corner, Pamela Davies, Malcom Goldstein, Joseph Jones and James Tenney; first complete 12 hour performance of Erick Satie's Vexations by The Pocket Theater Relay Team, poster. (#4), 1963 August 19, September 9 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Company. Two playbills, Sadlers Wells Theater, [no year] July 27, and Phoenix Theater. (#72), [no year] July 27, August 22 (Box 47 (Oversize))
    - 6 still photographs of Sap of Life, 1961 (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Art Book, hon-en historia from the Moderna Museet Stockholm, undated (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Derrier Le Mirroir, 9 Evenings - Theatre and Engineering, undated (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - The Hasty Papers, 1960 (Box 48 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook with clippings from vaious magazines and newpapers, some photographs, 2 (Box 49 (Oversize))
    - A collection of photographic works: Neighbors on the Block, Main Street, Growing Up Black, Open Space in the Inner City, The Lower East Side, undated; 5 (Box 50 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous oversize items, undated; 6 (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous oversize items, 6 (Box 102 (Oversize))
  - Oversize posters and art work
    - New York City Ballet, Stravinsky Festival., 1972 June 18-25 (Box 52 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham e la sua American Dance Company, Teatro La Fenice, poster., 1964 (Box 53 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham. John Cage, Robert Rauschenberg, Carolyn Brown, Viola Farber, and others. Spazio Estivo- Danza lirica (1958); Incontro Bizzarro (1958); Racconto (1963), poster, 1964. (#64), 1958, 1963, 1964 (Box 54 (Broadside))
    - Twyla Tharp Dance, Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster., 1984 January 24-February 12 (Box 55 (Broadside))
    - Teatr Laboratorium, Jerzy Grotowski, Ksiaze Niezlomny, poster. (#46), 1967 (Box 56 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, poster., undated (Box 57 (Broadside))
    - The Alvin Ailey Negro American Ballet and Dance Theatre, Comedie-Geneva, poster. (#17), 1968 May 20 (Box 58 (Broadside))
    - American Dance Theater and invited companies, New York State Theater, poster. (#52), 1965 (Box 59 (Broadside))
    - 5 New York Kvalar, Moderna Museet, 1964 September 8-14, poster. (Box 60 (Broadside))
    - Hon, Modern Museet, poster (#92), 1964 (Box 61 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham & Dance Company, Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster, 1969 January 5-16 (Box 62 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham & Dance Company, Brooklyn Academy of Music, poster, 1969 January 5-16 (Box 63 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham and American Dance Company, Teatro La Fenice, poster. (#71), 1964 (Box 64 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company w/John Cage, Stadsschouwburg - Arnhem, poster, undated (Box 65 (Broadside))
    - Leroi Jones' Slaveship, Chelsea Theater Center, poster., 1969 (Box 66 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham with Carolyn Brown and Viola Farber. [Tokyo tour], 1964, poster in Japanese. (#67) (Box 67 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham with Carolyn Brown and Viola Farber. [Tokyo tour], 1964, poster in Japanese. (#67) (Box 68 (Broadside))
    - Bang4. Robert Ashley, Gordon Mumma, Alvin Lucifer, David Behrman. Ann Arbor, Michigan, poster., 1967? April 29 (Box 69 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, John Cage and David Tudor, Club 49, Stiges. poster (#78), 1966 August 28 (Box 70 (Broadside))
    - The American Ballet Company. Dodocesimo Festival Dei Due Mondi. Teatro Nuovo. Directed by Eliot Feld, poster (#35; #36), 1969 (Box 71 (Broadside))
    - The American Ballet Company. Dodocesimo Festival Dei Due Mondi. Teatro Nuovo. Directed by Eliot Feld, poster (#35; #36), 1969 (Box 72 (Broadside))
    - The American Ballet Company. Dodocesimo Festival Dei Due Mondi. Teatro Nuovo. Directed by Eliot Feld, poster (#35; #36), 1969 (Box 73 (Broadside))
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company. Goscinny Wystep Baletu Amerykanskiego, poster in Polish. (#66), 1964 (Box 74 (Broadside))